Guide to the ACT UP New York records, 1969, 1982-1997 [bulk 1987-1995]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series XV. Addenda, 1985-1997, n.d.; 558269; 10 boxes
  - Conferences, 558277
    - First International Conference on AIDS, Atlanta, Georgia. Preliminary Program, circa 1985 Apr 14-17; 558279 (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Fifth International Conference on AIDS: The Scientific and Social Challenge, Montréal, Canada, circa 1989 Jun 4-9; 558280; Handouts (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Eleventh International Conference on AIDS, Vancouver, Canada, circa 1996 Jul; 558281; This folder contains information regarding ACT UP activities and demonstrations at this conference; it includes information on the following other chapters: Golden Gate, Paris, Philadelphia, and San Francisco.; Fliers, newsletters, press clippings, press releases, and reports (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Oct 18, 1996 Jul 25, n.d; 558282 (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - Demonstrations, 558283; Fliers, press clippings, press releases, stickers
    - Albany action, Albany, New York, 1990 Mar 28; 558284 (Box 233, Folder 12)
    - Crash the Market, 10th Anniversary action, circa 1997 Mar 24; 558285; The "Crash the Market" action corresponded with the tenth anniversary of ACT UP New York's founding. (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - Political funeral, circa 1996 Oct 13; 558286 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Queens Midtown Tunnel action and related action materials, circa 1995 Apr-Jul, n.d; 558287; Includes information on legal support (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Sunday in the Country with George [Pataki]" action, 1996 Feb 14, Apr-May; 558288 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Target Bush: 30 Days" information packet, circa 1991 Jul; 558289 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Drug pricing, 1996-1997, n.d.; 558290 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Ephemera, n.d.; 558291; The majority of the ephemera included here was created for various demonstrations.; Fliers, handbills, stickers (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits to submissions to IRS re: ACT UP/New York Inc., n.d.; 558292; Materials seemingly grouped by subject concerning ACT UP New York's activities.; Bound fliers, medical glossaries, press clippings (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Financial proposal, 1993 Jul, n.d; 558293 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Interact: News from all Over, 1990 Oct-1992 Jan; 558294; News from all Over was a summary of items received from national and international ACT UP chapters. (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - Majority Actions committee information packet, after 1989 Mar, before 1994 Jun; 558295 (Box 234, Folder 10)
  - Names Project Quilt, 1988 Oct; 558296 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  - Publications, 558297
    - Action 38-41, 43, 1996; 558298; Newsletter of ACT UP Paris (Box 234, Folder 12)
    - ACT UP Reports, 1989 Jun, 1991 [Mar?; 558299 (Box 234, Folder 13)
    - Handbook for Nonviolent Action, circa 1993 Jan, 1995 Aug, n.d; 558300 (Box 234, Folder 14)
    - Newsline, 1996 Jul/Aug; 558301; Produced by People with AIDS Coalition New York (PWAC NY). (Box 234, Folder 15)
    - Le Nouvel Observateur, 1985 Aug 9-15; 558302; This periodical is in French. (Box 234, Folder 16)
    - POZ, 1997 Mar; 558303 (Box 234, Folder 17)
    - Rolling Stone, 1989 May; 558304; This periodical is in French. (Box 234, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings, 558305
      - ACT UP and activists, 558306 (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - AIDS, 558307
        - AIDS Related Complex (ARC), n.d.; 558308 (Box 235, Folder 12)
        - As crime, n.d.; 558309 (Box 235, Folder 2)
        - Causes, n.d.; 558310 (Box 235, Folder 3)
        - Education, n.d.; 558311 (Box 235, Folder 4-5)
        - In general, n.d.; 558312 (Box 235, Folder 6-9)
        - Phobia, n.d.; 558313 (Box 235, Folder 11)
        - Related cancer, n.d.; 558314 (Box 235, Folder 10)
        - Testing, n.d.; 558315 (Box 235, Folder 13-14)
      - Africa, n.d.; 558316 (Box 235, Folder 15-16)
      - Africa, n.d.; 558317 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Babies and children, 558318 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Bath houses, n.d.; 558319 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Belle Glade, Florida, n.d.; 558320 (Box 236, Folder 4-5)
      - Birth rate, population control, n.d.; 558321 (Box 236, Folder 6)
      - Blood, n.d.; 558322 (Box 236, Folder 7)
      - Blood transfusion, n.d.; 558323 (Box 236, Folder 8)
      - Business and insurance, 558324 (Box 236, Folder 9)
      - Children and AIDS, 558325 (Box 236, Folder 10)
      - Clinics, n.d.; 558326 (Box 236, Folder 11)
      - Condoms, 558327 (Box 236, Folder 12)
      - Confidentiality, unique identifiers, n.d.; 558328 (Box 236, Folder 13)
      - Conservatives, n.d.; 558329 (Box 236, Folder 15-16)
      - Conservatives, conspiracy theory, n.d.; 558330 (Box 236, Folder 14)
      - Dimentia, n.d.; 558331 (Box 236, Folder 17)
      - Discrimination, n.d.; 558332 (Box 236, Folder 18)
      - DNCB, n.d.; 558333 (Box 236, Folder 19)
      - Doctors, n.d.; 558334 (Box 236, Folder 20)
      - Drug addiction, n.d.; 558335 (Box 236, Folder 21)
      - Drug users and AIDS, 558336 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Drug trials, n.d.; 558337 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Editorials, n.d.; 558338 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Editorials, letters, cartoons, 1987-1992, n.d.; 558339 (Box 238, Folder 1-2)
      - Education, 1988-1989; 558340 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Education/prevention, 1990-1991; 558341 (Box 238, Folder 4-5)
      - Education and youth, 558342 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Election '92, circa 1992; 558343 (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - Environmental toxins, n.d.; 558344 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 558345 (Box 237, Folder 6)
      - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), drugs, pharmaceutical companies, 558346 (Box 237, Folder 7)
      - Fundraising, 558347 (Box 237, Folder 8)
      - Gallo, Robert, n.d.; 558348 (Box 237, Folder 9)
      - General health, n.d.; 558349 (Box 237, Folder 10)
      - Healthcare, n.d.; 558350 (Box 237, Folder 11)
      - Hispanics, n.d.; 558351 (Box 237, Folder 12)
      - Homes, n.d.; 558352 (Box 237, Folder 13)
      - Homosexual rights, n.d.; 558353 (Box 237, Folder 14)
      - Hospitals, n.d.; 558354 (Box 237, Folder 15)
      - Housing and homeless, 558355 (Box 237, Folder 16)
      - Individual cases, 558356 (Box 237, Folder 17)
      - Individual cases, 558357 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - International, n.d.; 558358 (Box 239, Folder 2-4)
      - Koop, C. Everett, n.d.; 558359 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Legal, insurance, n.d.; 558360 (Box 239, Folder 6)
      - Lifestyle, culture, n.d.; 558361 (Box 239, Folder 7)
      - Malaria, n.d.; 558362 (Box 239, Folder 8)
      - Mass, Lawrence: MD, author, n.d.; 558363 (Box 239, Folder 9)
      - Media, n.d.; 558364 (Box 239, Folder 10)
      - Media committee press packets, 1991 Nov-1992 Jun; 558365 (Box 239, Folder 11)
      - Medical overview, n.d.; 558366 (Box 239, Folder 12-16)
      - Medical research, n.d.; 558367 (Box 239, Folder 17-18)
      - Military, n.d.; 558368 (Box 239, Folder 19)
      - Military, n.d.; 558369 (Box 240, Folder 1-2)
      - Needle exchange, n.d.; 558370 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - New York State, n.d.; 558371 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - National Institutes of Health (NIH), n.d.; 558372 (Box 240, Folder 6)
      - Police vs. gay and lesbian community, 558373 (Box 237, Folder 19)
      - Politics, law, n.d.; 558374 (Box 240, Folder 7-8)
      - Politicians, doctors, etc., n.d.; 558375 (Box 240, Folder 9)
      - Prison, n.d.; 558376 (Box 240, Folder 10)
      - Professions, n.d.; 558377 (Box 240, Folder 11)
      - Religlions, n.d.; 558378 (Box 240, Folder 12-13)
      - Reporting, n.d.; 558379 (Box 240, Folder 14)
      - Research, n.d.; 558380 (Box 240, Folder 15)
      - Russian newspaper, n.d.; 558381 (Box 240, Folder 16)
      - Sexual mores, n.d.; 558382 (Box 240, Folder 17)
      - Science education, n.d.; 558383 (Box 240, Folder 18)
      - Social issues, n.d.; 558384 (Box 240, Folder 19-22)
      - Statistics, growth, n.d.; 558385 (Box 240, Folder 23)
      - Transmission, n.d.; 558386 (Box 240, Folder 24)
      - Transmission, n.d.; 558387 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Treatment, n.d.; 558388 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Veneral disease, n.d.; 558389 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Victims and survivors, 558390 (Box 241, Folder 4)
      - Virus, n.d.; 558391 (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Volunteers, hospice, n.d.; 558392 (Box 241, Folder 6)
      - Women, n.d.; 558393 (Box 241, Folder 7)
      - Workplace, n.d.; 558394 (Box 241, Folder 8)
      - World Health Organization (WHO), n.d.; 558395 (Box 241, Folder 9)
      - Youth, n.d.; 558396 (Box 241, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1991, 1995-1997; 558397 (Box 241, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 558398 (Box 237, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 558399 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - YELL [Youth Education Life Line], 1992 Feb 24, 1994 Dec, circa 1997; 558400; Postcard with photograph attached, 'zines (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986-1988, 1992, 1994-1996, n.d; 558401 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1987 Mar-1991 Nov, n.d; 558402 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1987-1989, 1992-1993, 1995, n.d; 558403 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 558404 (Box 242, Folder 5-12)
  - Miscellaneous incomplete materials, n.d.; 558405 (Box 242, Folder 13)